Guide to the Edward W. Sites Papers, 1958-2019 UA.90.F109
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Edward W. Sites Papers
1958-2019
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Sites, Edward W.
UA.90.F109
36.25 Linear Feet (29 boxes)
Edward Sites Ph.D. was a social worker and faculty member of the University of Pittsburgh's School of Social Work from 1966 until becoming professor emeritus in 2006. This collection documents the history of the School of Social Work during Sites' career through reports, memoranda, publications, and other records.
Biography
Edward Sites, Ph.D. is a social worker and emeritus faculty member of the University of Pittsburgh.
Sites began his academic career at the University of Pittsburgh's School of Social Work in 1966. During his time on the faculty, he served as the school's Director of Admission and Financial Aid; Chair of the Children and Youth Concentration; Coordinator of the Joint Master of Social Work/Master of Divinity degree program with the Pittsburgh Theological Seminary; Coordinator of the Home School Visitor Program; a member of the Doctoral faculty; and the founding Principal Investigator of the Pennsylvania Child Welfare Education and Research Programs. Sites taught numerous subjects, specifically child welfare policy and grant proposal writing. In 2006, he was named a professor emeritus. Outside the classroom, Sites serves as the Facilitator of Allegheny County's Act 33 Child Fatality/Near Fatality Review Team and works on special projects with the School of Social Work.
Sites earned a bachelor's degree from Gettysburg College in 1962 and a Master's in Social Work from the University of Pittsburgh in 1964. Before joining the University of Pittsburgh faculty, he was a social worker with the Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare's Office for Children and Youth from 1962 to 1966 and a Sociology instructor at Wilson College from 1965 to 1966.
Scope and Content Notes
The Edward Sites Papers contain the collected works and papers of Professor Sites. The collection spans from 1958 to 2019 and contains records pertaining to the School of Social Work at the University of Pittsburgh. Topics covered in this collection include Administration for Children Youth and Families; Child Development/Child Care; Children and Youth Cluster; Long Range Planning; Promotion and Tenure Committee; and Statistics on the School of Social Work, among others. It also includes School of Social Work accreditation reports to the Council on Social Work Education and faculty meeting minutes. Audiovisual recordings of lectures, interviews, and trainings on numerous subjects are located at the end of the collection.
Material specific to Sites' career include his incoming and outgoing professional correspondence and memoranda pertaining to the administration of the School of Social Work and University of Pittsburgh, as well as other organizations affiliated with Sites such as the Pennsylvania Rehabilitation Center. Also included are administrative files and reports for many of Sites' projects including "Steeltown Fathers: Rearing Children in an Era of Industrial Decline" and a collaboration with the Pittsburgh AIDS Taskforce to help train public school staff and others who were likely to work closely with youth at a high risk of exposure to AIDS.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Edward Sites in 2006, 2008, 2019, and 2023.
Related Materials
School of Social Work, Office Files, University of Pittsburgh, 1953-1955, UA.90.18.2, University Archives, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Division of Social Work, Marion Hathway Files, University of Pittsburgh, 1930-1938, UA.90.18.1, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Elizabeth Elmer Papers, 1959-1993, UA.90.F86, University Archives, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Rosalie Cohen Papers, 1965-1985, UA.90.F57, University Archives, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Social work education -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Social workers -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; College teachers -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Social work with children -- Study and teaching -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Audiotapes; Correspondence; Faculty papers; Grant proposals; Memorandums; Minutes (Administrative records); Reports; Video recordings (physical artifacts); Sites, Edward W.; University of Pittsburgh. Graduate School of Social Work -- Faculty; University of Pittsburgh. Graduate School of Social Work -- History
- Academic Review, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Accreditation; Response of a School of Social Work to Change, 1971 (Box 1, Volume 2)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume II, 1977 (Box 1, Volume 3)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume I, 1982 (Box 1, Volume 4)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume I, Dean Plutchok's corrected copy, 1982 (Box 1, Volume 5)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume II, 1982 (Box 1, Volume 6)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume II, Dean Plutchok's corrected copy, 1982 (Box 1, Volume 7)
- Accreditation Review Authorization, Council on Social Work Education, Eligibility Forms A-L, 1988 (Box 1, Volume 8)
- Accreditation Committee, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume I, 1988 (Box 1, Volume 10)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume II, 1988 (Box 1, Volume 11)
- Accreditation, Response of Site Visit Team and Response of School to Council on Social Work Education, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume I, Bachelor of Arts in Social Work, 1995 (Box 1, Volume 13)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume II, Bachelor of Arts in Social Work, 1995 (Box 1, Volume 14)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume III, Bachelor of Arts in Social Work, 1995 (Box 1, Volume 15)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume I, Masters in Social Work, 1995 (Box 2, Volume 1)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume II A, Masters in Social Work, 1995 (Box 2, Volume 2)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume II B, Masters in Social Work, 1995 (Box 2, Volume 3)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume III, Masters in Social Work, 1995 (Box 2, Volume 4)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Bachelor of Arts in Social Work & Masters in Social Work Eligibility Forms, A-F, 1995 (Box 2, Volume 5)
- Accreditation, Response of Site Visit Team (Bachelor of Arts in Social Work & Masters in Social Work), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Accreditation, Trustee Institutional Review, University of Pittsburgh, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Accreditation, Council on Social Work Education, Education & Accreditation Standards (EPAS), 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Accreditation, Self-Study Report, Volume I (Standards 1-8), 2004 (Box 2, Volume 9)
- Admission to Graduate Schools of Social Work, Council on Social Work Education, 1965 (Box 2, Volume 10)
- Adoption, Special Needs, background materials for videotape titled Special Needs Adoption (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Administration, Social, 1978-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Admissions: Non-Bachelors Admission to Masters in Social Work Program (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Alumnae(i), Distinguished Alumnae(i) Awards I (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Alumnae(i), Distinguished Alumnae(i) Awards II (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Alumnae(i), Distinguished Alumnae(i) Awards, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Alumnae(i), Distinguished Alumnae(i) Awards, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Teaching Grant, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Advanced Graduate Course Content, Children, Youth and Families, Judith A. Martin, Ed., 1982 (Box 3, Volume 2-3)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Traineeship Grant, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Traineeship Grant, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Teaching Grant, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Traineeship Grant, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Teaching Grant, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Grants, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Grants, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Grants, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Traineeship Grant, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Grants, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Grants, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Grants, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Administration for Children Youth and Families, Grants, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Admissions Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Admissions, Black Student Initiatives, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Advisee File, Edward W. Sites (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Advising Task Force, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Advising, Faculty, 1969-1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Advising Faculty, Including several papers by Edward W. Sites, 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- AIDS Project, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- AIDS Project, Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Alumnae(i) Newsletters, School of Social Work, 1971-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Alumnae(i) Newsletters, School of Social Work, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Alumnae(i) Newsletters, School of Social Work, 1998-2012 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Basis of Social Functioning, Lectures by Professor Allan Kline, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Board of Trustees, Pitt; Remarks by Edward W. Sites, October 18, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Book Reviews (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Bradford, University of Pittsburgh at – Masters in Social Work Program, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Child Development, Office of; Interdisciplinary Fellowship Advisory Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Chancellor's Public Service Award, Edward W. Sites, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Chancellor's Task Force on Early Childhood Development, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Council on Early Childhood Development, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Chancellor's Teaching Award, Edward W. Sites, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Chapel Hill University of North Carolina Workshops, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Child Abuse and Neglect, Interdisciplinary Project, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
- Child Abuse Training Grant, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Child Development/Child Care Awards, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Child Development/Child Care, Planning Document, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Child Development/Child Care, Program Profile, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Child Development/Child Care, Self-Study, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Child Development/Child Care, Faculty Workload, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Child Development/Child Care Transition to the School of Social Work, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Child Development, Office of, 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
- Child Development, Office of, 1995-2008 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Child Development, Office of, 1995-2012 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Child Welfare Conference, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Child Welfare Education and Research Center Proposal, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Child Welfare, Field of, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Child Welfare History, School of Social Work, Univ. of Pittsburgh, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Child Welfare Interdisciplinary Training Grant, 1991-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
- Child Welfare Interdisciplinary Studies, 1991-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
- Children's Services Project Advisory Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Child Welfare Services Training Institute, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Child Welfare Training: PITT Project, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Children and Youth Cluster Concept, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Children and Youth Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Children and Youth Faculty, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Children and Youth Cluster Faculty Meetings, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Children and Youth Cluster Lab, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Children and Youth Faculty, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Children and Youth Services Cluster, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Children's Lobby (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Church Related Field Placements, Masters in Social Work (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Cockerill, Eleanor (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Commission for Children, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Committee Assignments, School of Social Work, 1969-2018 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Community Laboratory, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Community Organization, 1966-1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Community Organization, Planning and Administration Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Community Organization and Social Administration, 1998-2006 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Continuing Education (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
- Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1968-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Child Welfare Education Baccalaureates Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Child Welfare Education Baccalaureates Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Child Welfare Education Baccalaureates Correspondence, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Correspondence, 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Child Welfare Training Program Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Child Welfare Training Program Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Child Welfare Training Program Correspondence, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Proposal - Original, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Volume 4)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Volume 5)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Volume 6)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Volume 7)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Volume 8)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Volume 9)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Volume 10)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Volume 11)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Volume 12)
- Child Welfare Education for Leadership Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 13, Volume 13)
- Course Evaluation, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Course Outlines (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Council on Social Work Education, Annual Program Meeting – Presentations (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Curriculum Committee, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Child Welfare Education Network, Final Report, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Child Welfare Interdisciplinary Network, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Child Welfare League of America Regional Conference, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Direct Practice (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Disaster Intervention (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Doctoral Program (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Doctoral Program (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
- Doctoral Program 60th Anniversary, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Economics and Family Relationships (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Educational Policies Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Educational Policies Committee, 1994-2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Ethnicity Seminar, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Excellence Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Extended Masters of Social Work Program, 1980-1984 (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
- Faculty Executive Committee, 1972-1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Faculty Executive Committee, 1969-2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Family Foundations Evaluation (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Family Life Task Force, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Father's Project, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Father's Project, 1987-1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Father's Project, 1988-1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Father's Project, Final Report, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Field Instruction Manual, School of Social Work, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Field Instruction Manuals, School of Social Work, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Gartland, Ruth, 1893-1946 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Group Home Project, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Harassment, Sexual (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Health and Mental Health (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Health Survey, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Hull House Revival (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Human Relations Committee, School of Social Work, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Industrial Rehabilitation, Research Report, School of Social Work, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Industrial Social Work (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Industrial Social Work Program, School of Social Work, E. Gregory de Silva, Ph.D., Associate Professor, Director Scrapbook, 1978-1992 (Box 29, Item 1)
- Institute for Peer Education (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Institutional Advancement, School of Social Work, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Interdisciplinary Child Welfare Training, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Iowa Neglect Study, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
- Iowa Neglect Study, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Jaffe, Lois (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Jaffe, Lois, Death and Dying, Papers and Syllabus (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Lehrman, Louis J. (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Library Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Licensure, Pennsylvania Alliance, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Long Range Planning, School of Social Work, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Long Range Planning, School of Social Work, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Long Range Planning, School of Social Work, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Long Range Planning, School of Social Work, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Long Range Planning, School of Social Work, 1994-2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Loysville Youth Development Center, Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Master of Social Work Program Committee, 1983-1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Mediation Center Pittsburgh Evaluation, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
- Mental Health/Mental Retardation Juvenile Court Task Force, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Memoranda, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Memoranda, 1968-1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Memoranda, 1974-1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Memoranda, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Memoranda, 1979-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Memoranda, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Memoranda, 1986-1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Memoranda, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Memoranda, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Memoranda, 1994-1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Memoranda, 1997-1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Memoranda, 1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Memoranda, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Memoranda, 2003-2006 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Myers, William (Box 21, Folder 5)
- National Association of Social Workers, Southwest Pennsylvania Division, Photos, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Neighborhoods, Pittsburgh (Box 21, Folder 7)
- National Institute of Mental Health Disaster Intervention, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- National Institute of Mental Health, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- National Institute of Mental Health, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Peer Faculty Review, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Perkins Loans Paper, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Pittsburgh Theological Seminary, Joint Masters of Social Work/Ministry Division, 1967-2014 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Plutchok, George (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Policy Manual, School of Social Work, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Policy Manual, School of Social Work, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Poverty and Associated Problems Concentration, 1973-1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Pre-Social Work Guild Student Organization Scrapbook, 1950 (Box 29, Item 2)
- Press Conference, Child Welfare Education Training, September 10, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Productivity, Faculty, 1976-2005 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Profession, Attributes of (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Professional Skills Task Force, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Promotion and Tenure, 1988-2003 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Promotion and Tenure Committee, 1978-1997 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Promotion and Tenure Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Promotion and Tenure Committee, Fall 2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Promotion and Tenure Committee, 2001-2003 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Psychologist Examiners, Pennsylvania Board of, 1979-1984 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Race and Social Problems, Center on (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Rubash Lecture, 1998-2010 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Rubenstein, Jack Group Work, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Secretarial, 1985-2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- School of Social Work, History of (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
- School of Social Work, History of (Box 24, Folder 1)
- School of Social Work History, Centennial Observance, 2017-2019 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- School of Social Work History, Centennial Research Background Materials and Documents (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Sites, Edward W., Articles, Reports, and Remarks (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
- Sites, Edward W., Curriculum Vitae and Biographical Information (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Social Welfare, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1988-1992 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1995-1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 1998-2002 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Social Work Faculty Meetings, 2004-2006 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Social Work Faculty Papers (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Social Work Licensure, PA, 1987-2004 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Social Worker of the Year, PA National Association of Social Workers, Edward W. Sites, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Social and Rehabilitation Services, United States, 1974-1981 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1958-1966 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Statistics, School of Social Work, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 11)